http://www.datasecurityinc.com/privacy.html

Search form
Search
1.800.225.7554
Main menuHOMESECURITY RESOURCES - Information Security -- Who's at risk? -- How to erase a HDD -- How to destroy a HDD -- Solid state vs. Hard Disk
- Degaussing facts -- Why degauss? -- Misconceptions -- Benefits -- Is it really erased? -- Operator safety - Guidance & regulation -- Government: --- NSA --- DoD --- NIST --- GLB Act --- HIPPADEGAUSSERS - Which degausser is right for me? - All Degaussers -- HD-5T Degausser -- HPM-2 Degausser -- LM-1 Degausser -- LM-1C Degausser - Mobile -- HD-5T Degausser -- HPM-2 Degausser - High volume -- LM-1 Degausser -- LM-1C Degausser - Degauss & destroy duos -- High volume: --- LM-1 & DX-8 -- Mobile: --- HD-5T & DB-4000
--- HPM-2 & DB-6000
- Refurbished - Accessories -- Field CheckR -- Compact Field CheckR -- Cases -- Carts -- Warranty -- Certification DESTROYERS - Which destroyer is right for me? - Hard Drive -- DB-4000 Destruction
-- DB-6000 Destruction
-- DX-8 Destruction - Solid State -- SSMD-2mm Solid State Media Disintegrator -- CR-4KR Solid State Media Cracker - Degauss & destroy duos -- High volume: --- LM-1 & DF-4 --- LM-1C & DF-4 --- LM-1 & DX-8 -- Mobile: --- HD-5T & DB-4000 --- HPM-2 & DB-6000 - Refurbished - Accessories -- Carts -- Cases -- WarrantySERVICES - User Manuals - Technical Assistance - Degausser Testing - Certification - Warranty Renewal - Recycle & Upgrade - Erasure Service - REQUEST A QUOTEABOUT US - Contact Us - History - Why buy DSI - Environment - Intl Distributors - Privacy Policy - Careers
HOME HomeSECURITY RESOURCES Security ResourcesInformation SecurityWho's at risk?How to erase a HDDHow to destroy a HDDSolid state vs. Hard Disk Degaussing factsWhy degauss?MisconceptionsBenefitsIs it really erased?Operator safetyGuidance & regulationGovernment:NSADoDNISTGLB ActHIPPADEGAUSSERSWhich degausser is right for me?All DegaussersHD-5T DegausserHPM-2 DegausserLM-1 DegausserLM-1C Degausser LM-1C DegausserMobileHD-5T DegausserHPM-2 DegausserHigh volumeLM-1 Degausser LM-1 DegausserLM-1C Degausser LM-1C DegausserDegauss & destroy duosHigh volume:LM-1 & DX-8Mobile:HD-5T & DB-4000 HPM-2 & DB-6000 RefurbishedAccessoriesField CheckRCompact Field CheckR Compact Field CheckRCasesCartsWarrantyCertification DESTROYERS DestroyersWhich destroyer is right for me?Hard DriveDB-4000 Destruction DB-6000 Destruction DX-8 DestructionSolid StateSSMD-2mm Solid State Media DisintegratorCR-4KR Solid State Media Cracker Open Solid State MediaDegauss & destroy duosHigh volume:LM-1 & DF-4LM-1C & DF-4LM-1 & DX-8Mobile:HD-5T & DB-4000HPM-2 & DB-6000RefurbishedAccessoriesCartsCasesWarrantySERVICES ServicesUser ManualsTechnical AssistanceDegausser TestingCertificationWarranty RenewalRecycle & UpgradeErasure ServiceREQUEST A QUOTEABOUT US About UsContact Us Contact PageHistoryWhy buy DSIEnvironmentIntl DistributorsPrivacy PolicyCareers Careers
PRIVACY POLICY
Data Security, Inc. has a firm commitment to personal privacy. Any personal information collected is provided by website users voluntarily. Information collected includes but is not limited to names, addresses, phone numbers. This data is used internally by the home office, only to respond to customer requests or to process orders. Data Security, Inc. will never sell, or otherwise disclose your personal information outside of the organization.
Data Security, Inc. is an equal opportunity employer.
Data Security, Inc. complies with the six affirmative action requirements in 41C.F.R 60-741.5(a) of Executive Order 11246.
CONTACT  US
INTERNATIONAL  SALES
GIVE  US  FEEDBACK
PRIVACY  POLICY
© Copyright 2014 Data Security, Inc. – 300 S. 7th St., Lincoln, Nebraska 68508 – 1(800) 225-7554 or 1 (402) 434-5959 – Fax: (402) 434-3291
